# Doug Watro

DougWatro@gmail.com

DougWatro.com

631-681-0941

#### LANGUAGES

HTML5

CSS / SASS

JAVASCRIPT / ES6 / JSX

PHP

JAVA

C + +

C#

#### **SKILLS**

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPMENT

UX DESIGN

RESPONSIVE WEB DEVELOPMENT

CODE OPTIMIZATION

# SOFTWARE / FRAMEWORKS

REACT / REDUX

ATOM / DREAMWEAVER

WORDPRESS

NPM

BOOTSTRAP

 ${\sf MONGODB}$ 

EXPRESS / NODEJS

ADOBE CC

#### GOALS

To learn all I can about fullstack web development, and keep on the bleeding edge of new technologies.

Use my experiences in computer science and game development to offer a different perspective on UX and the art of web programming.

Work with passionate professionals in the exciting, fast paced, always changing world of web development.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **DESIGN ASSISTANT | MAGIC SPELL STUDIOS**

FEBRUARY 2014 - AUGUST 2014

Conceptualized and designed 3D game levels to be integrated within a larger game world. Work among a team of 20 to design the overall direction of the project. Designed small levels to be used in promotional material.

# LEVEL DESIGNER/3D ARTIST | IGM GRAD DEPARTMENT

WINTER - SPRING 2015

Worked with a team of grad students to assist them in completing their capstone project. Acted as the sole level designer for their 3D topdown action tower defense game. Worked with other artist to model and texture assets when needed.

## INDECISION BETA APP RELEASE | GOOGLE PLAY STORE

LATE 2016 - EARLY 2017

Designed, programmed, and began public beta tests of an Android App on the Google Play Store.

### **EDUCATION**

ROCHESTER INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY 2012 - 2017 BS | GAME DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT